This series is crafted for the purpose of entertainment.
All characters, behaviors, settings, and events depicted in this drama are entirely fictitious.
They are not designed to allude to any particular entity, occupation, or group of people.
Viewer discretion is advised.
[North Star Entertainment]
[7HD Channel]
[iQIYI]
[Present]
♫Where’s that love people are saying?♫
♫To always be by each other’s sides♫
♫The love that’s willing to sacrifice everything♫
♫Everything even my own life♫
♫Do they really exist? I’d rather not believe it♫
♫I don’t think I’ll ever fall for anyone♫
♫Love? I don’t find it interesting♫
♫Sorry about that♫
♫But then who are you?♫
♫To make my heart keep fluttering♫
♫Please tell me♫
♫What’s happening with my heart?♫
♫It can’t be, why am I feeling this?♫
♫Oh, my heart is pounding so fast♫
♫Time freezes whenever I see you♫
♫I wonder why every time you smile♫
♫Something in your eyes make me go weak♫
♫Oh no, this is real–it’s not a dream♫
♫Or is the love that people are saying...♫
♫Is it you?♫
[Flaming Chains of Love]
[Previously]
If you find a pink shell, you’ll get to make one wish.
There it is!
[Thunder]
May everyone be happy!
[Bua]: A bad storm is coming. You’d better stay here tonight, Young Master.
Does that mean we won’t be able to go back until tomorrow?
[Fai]: Will there be any storm today?
[Bua]: No, Miss.
Then, go tell Uncle Boonsong this.
Don’t tell me you want to go back right now.
Nope.
[Panee]: I already warned you not to cause Fai any trouble.
What do you want me to do then?
[Akanee]: Fai is here to help the Little One.
There’s nothing to worry about now.
[Fai]: Are you going to leave me here?
[Kaphrao]: Then, get up. Get up!
How old are you this year?
22.
You’re an adult now, a grown-ass woman.
You’re not a kid anymore.
You don’t need to do everything my aunt says.
If you don’t want to do it, just say it out loud.
so that you won’t trouble yourself later.
As if Miss Panee would let me say no to her.
Are you trying to get me scolded even more?
Just do as I say. Leave the rest to me.
How can I trust you?
Whatever, it’s your choice.
I’m leaving.
Me too, but…let me drop you off.
Whatever.
Why are you following me? Just go home.
I need to make sure you won’t sneak out to suck up to my dad.
Urgh!!!
Phrao!
Nod!
How did you get here?
I’m here to surprise you.
- Aww, you’re as sweet as ever.
- Right?
Hey, you’re too skinny.
Waiting for your treat.
Sure! Just name the date.
Okay.
Aww, miss you so much!
I remember you told me you live here.
I’ve moved to Surat now.
We can meet more often from now on.
Why did you move here?
My relative is opening a hotel here, and also plans to open a restaurant; so I’m here to help.
That sounds great.
Well, what a coincidence.
I think it’s more like destiny.
If you’re done catching up, hurry and get back to work.
What work? It’s off the clock now.
It’s overtime work, to make up for what I helped you earlier.
What?
I couldn’t get any work done because I was helping you with the lawn mowing.
Got loads of them piling up over my head.
- But I’ll go to work tomorrow any–
- Phrao.
Just get on with your work.
I’ll come see you again.
We have plenty of time to meet up after this.
Don’t you think so?
I’ll go wait at the office.
It’s okay.
So, what work is it?
I want to talk to you about the resort.
Yeah?
We’ll create ecotourism there starting with a homestay at the locals’ houses including Lom’s cabin too, right?
That’s right. We’ve already talked about this.
Well, I’ll start drafting the plan then.
Is that all?
What about the second project? When should we start?
Look, do we really need to talk about this now?
We haven’t even started the first one yet.
So that we’ll have more time to prepare.
Why? Are you mad because I interrupted your precious time with your friend?
You’re damn right! So what?
Why can’t she just find a damn job in Bangkok?
Hey! Where do you think you’re going?
Home!
You dragged me here just to say that? Hey!
That’s it? Why now?
It’s more like destiny. Destiny…Destiny…Destiny.
Obviously not just a friend.
This one is good.
Thank you.
Nod, can I have it?
Only this once.
Thank you!
Phrao! Where are you, Phrao?
Over here, Nod.
Thanks a lot, Nod.
No problem. I’ll wait outside then.
You’re the sweetest!
Nod! What are you doing here?
I bought you sticky rice and grilled pork skewers–your favourite.
Wow, thank you!
I’m out looking for seafood ingredients for my relative’s restaurant.
Oh, you’ve come to the right place. I’ll take you to the fisherman’s wharf.
Let’s take my car then. You can be my navigator.
Sure!
Let’s go.
Can I eat them in your car?
Of course. They’re really good.
I’m not sharing then.
Who’s that?
Can you please remove those too, so it won’t look so messy?
Bua.
Where’s Kaphrao?
Oh, she went to the fisherman’s wharf with her friend.
Friend?
Yes, her friend came early in the morning.
I think she said she’s looking for seafood ingredients.
Which friend? What’s her name? What does she look like?
I think she’s called Nod. If I’m not wrong, I mean.
As for her appearance, she looks so pretty and neat, Young Master.
They’re taking really good care of each other.
She even brought Miss Phrao breakfast. Miss Phrao also seems to be very fond of her.
So, should I go get Miss Phrao for you?
No need. It’s not like I care.
That bloody loafer, came here every f***ing day!
Here, I’ll show you how they’re sorting them out. You can be sure all seafood is fresh here.
That’s lots of them!
This is the first station. They’re sorting out small fish and baitfish.
This station is for medium-size fish. We have plenty for you to choose from.
They’re all fresh from the sea. Look there.
It’s nothing. Let’s go.
This station is for big fish.
- So big!
- Right?
Have you ever seen this one? We have various types of fish here.
Nod!
Here you go.
Wow.
I’ll give it to my relative and see what we can do with it.
Thanks. I’ll also help talk to Uncle Ak for any possible discount.
Do you usually take care of the work here at the fisherman’s wharf?
Not really, I’m actually Fai’s assistant. I just do whatever I’m assigned to.
Uncle wants me to try out everything before deciding which work I like the most.
Why is he so nice to you?
If I hadn’t known, I would’ve thought you were one of his daughters who owns this place.
Geez, don’t say that. Fai already hates me to her guts these days.
Anyway, do you have anything else to do today?
I’m working half-day today.
Let’s go find something to eat then.
Sure.
[Nod]: Should we go now?
[Phrao]: Mhm.
[Phrao]: I need to grab my bag first.
[Nod]: Sure.
[Nod]: What do you want to eat? I’m starving.
[Phrao]: Look, tumblers.
The colours look so sweet.
Yeah, very sweet.
Oh, this one!
Yeah, or this one.
[Phrao]: It’s so cute. Baby pink.
Should we get them?
[Nod]: Yes, but I’ll pay.
[Phrao]: Aww, thank you, Sugar Mummy.
[Nod]: No problem, babe.
[Phrao]: Maybe, I should get one of these bags.
[Nod]: They’re pretty.
[Phrao]: And big too.
[Phrao]: Look.
[Nod]: Huh?
[Phrao]: Isn’t it cute?
[Nod]: Yeah, so cute.
Right? Wow…
[Phrao]: Hey, this one’s cute!
[Phrao]: So cold.
[Phrao]: Freezing?
[Nod]:It’s so good!
Let me try it too.
[Nod]: How is it?
[Phrao]: Awesome!
How’s the drink?
[Phrao]: Try it.
[Phrao]: Like it?
[Phrao]: This one is good too.
Looking so bloody happy, huh?
Fai!
Oh, look who’s here. What a coincidence.
What are you doing here? Don’t tell me you’re stalking me.
What? Who’s stalking?
I’m here to get some toys for the mine worker's kid, and just came across this air hockey here.
When I was a kid, no one could beat me at it.
Should we play a round then?
One more?
That’s enough. I’m hungry. I still need to go back to do the laundry.
That’s great. I’m hungry too. It’s my treat this time.
[Phrao]: What should we order?
- [Nod]: They all look tasty.
Look, they have squids too. You like them, don’t you?
Let’s order Squid Tom Yum then.
You remember?
One squid Tom Yum, please.
I remember everything about you.
But I don’t remember a thing. I can’t remember what you like to eat.
I like Kaphrao (holy basil). I’ll have one stir-fried crispy pork with holy basil, please.
What about you, Miss Fai?
ike Kaphrao too.
I’ll have stir-fried crispy pork in extra size with lots of holy basil leaves, please.
Since when have you liked holy basil?
I’ve always liked it.
Really?
So, we’ll have one pot of rice, stir-fried crispy pork with lots of holy basil in extra size, and squid Tom Yum.
That’s all, right?
That’d be all.
I’m starving.
You seem to know her well, Nod.
Of course, I do. We used to eat and sleep together for many years.
What about you? How long have you known her?
Well, since she was seven–long before she moved to Bangkok and met you there.
So, I guess you must know about her Phi Jah (Big Sis).
Nod!
Why?
Who’s Phi Jah?
It’s the person she likes.
That’s weird. She’s never told you about that?
Nod, stop it.
Are you two really close?
Nod, it was just a joke–why did you bring it up? I wasn’t being serious.
It’s nothing. We were just joking around.
The food is so slow. I’ll go to the loo first.
She took you out and ditched you there.
What would you do if I wasn’t around to drop you home?
Something urgent came up for her. Wasn’t it you who offered to drop me home in the first place?
Hold on. Got something to ask you.
What now? Can it wait until tomorrow?
But I want to know it now.
So selfish.
Hey, wait!
Who the hell is Jah?
What?
Is she someone you’re seeing? Someone you like? Or your first girlfriend?
And how long have you known her?
Why on earth would you want to know?
Because I want to. Does my dad know about this?
None of your business. Move!
Hey! Can’t you just tell me? Hey!
Come any closer and I’ll call the police to arrest you for trespassing.
Go away!
Geez, I was just asking.
And I’m not telling you!
What’s so secret? Would it kill you to say it?
Who the hell?
[Phone ringing]
What, Boss Rose?
Why do you sound so grumpy?
I just want to place an order for seafood.
Din and I are going to have a seafood party for our workers.
We’d like you to send us some shrimps and crabs.
Okay, I’ll have someone take care of it by tomorrow morning.
Is that all?
Come on, don’t hang up on me so fast.
Did you have a fight with Miss Phrao? Is that why you’re so grumpy?
What? Who says I love that silly Gremlin?
Besides, her friend just slipped out today that she already has someone she likes.
I see, someone is being heartbroken.
I told you I don’t like her!
All right, I heard that. You don’t have to be so pissed.
Listen Fai, you should try to be nice to her. Don’t just keep picking on her, or else she’ll hate you.
So what? Who cares?
That’s too bad. I was actually going to give you some advice on how to pursue a girl–
to make Miss Phrao like you.
What should I do then?
I thought you said you don’t like her.
Well, just for interest’s sake.
If you like her
and want her to love you,
you must try to please her and be nice to her.
Take her out to wonderful places and to eat something delicious.
She’ll definitely fall for you.
So, any other details?
Let me suggest my “3As” technique.
The one that’s perfect for you is “A for (being) attentive”.
You need to find out what she likes and try to pamper her with those things.
Quit picking on her, and only do whatever she pleases. Got it?
You two already went to the island.
Have you come up with any ideas to pitch me?
We both agree that this project should be divided into two phases.
For the first phase, we’ll start by providing a simple homestay service.
So that local villagers could take part in it.
It’ll also help generate more income for them.
We can use Miss Lom and Miss Blew’s cabin as our selling point.
And back it up with the Princess’s story when she used to stay there.
That’s a brilliant idea.
But will it affect the villagers’ way of living? Have you thought about that too?
Yes, that’s why we’d like to start with only a few cabins first. Then, we’ll see the response.
After that, we can adjust the plan along the way so it won’t affect the calm and peaceful life of local people there.
And to make it more interesting, I think we should also have a diving activity.
I’m sure it’ll help attract more tourists to come to the island.
What a perfect combination.
One is to look after the cozy accommodation.
The other is to take care of tourist activities.
I approve of this project.
Now, you two should write a full business plan and show it to me after this.
Give me your best shot.
[Rose]: If you like her and want her to love you, you must try to please her and be nice to her.
Take her out to wonderful places and to eat something delicious.
She’ll definitely fall for you.
Anything on what I told you to find out?
Listen, Young Master. I didn’t just ask around but I also used my nosy skill to pry out more information.
I sneaked into Miss Phrao’s room and took a quick look at her purse.
I found a picture of her and her dad when she was a kid.
It was taken at the dam. If I’m not mistaken, I think it also has a water park there.
A water park?
Yes, I remember Miss Phrao once told me she wanted to go there.
Still love playing like a kid as I thought.
Come on, Young Master. Anyone would want to act like a kid once in a while.
Unlike someone who’s always working her butt off.
All right then, thanks a lot. And don’t tell her I asked you about this.
Geez, Young Master. You can trust me. I won’t say anything–my lips are sealed.
- Enjoy your food then.
- Yes.
I want you to go to the dam with me.
The dam?
Mhm.
Just want to check it out in case we might get some ideas for our project.
But if you don’t want to, I can go alone.
Of course, I’ll go!
I want to go there. When I was a kid, my dad used to take me there.
You want to go?
Mhm.
Then, I’m not going.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Beg me first.
Then, I’m not going. So annoying!
Hey, wait! Hold on!
Let’s go then. I was only kidding back there.
Then, beg me first.
Come with me, please. Pleaseee.
Mhm.
And make sure you wear something pretty.
Otherwise, people might think I’m there with a servant.
Foul mouth!
But since you’re cute,
I’ll forgive you.
What are you up to, my pretty lady?
Come give me a hug.
Are you going out somewhere, dear?
Do you need me for anything, Auntie?
My friend and her daughter will come to our house today.
I want you to take her daughter out and show her around.
Does it have to be today?
Yes, isn’t it your day off today?
Or do you have other plans?
Well, I…
Please do me a favour and show her around. Just do it for me.
Could it be some other days?
I already promised it to Jinda, dear.
If you don’t do it, my friend might see me as someone who kept going back on my words.
Do it for me. Please.
Okay.
My good girl.
I’ll make some desserts for you.
Miss Phrao, you look so pretty!
Wow, can you turn around?
Wow, I almost couldn’t recognise you! So pretty indeed.
Trust me, if Young Master sees you in this dress, her jaw will definitely drop.
No way.
I’m going then.
Okay, bye! Good luck!
You’re here early.
I’m afraid I can’t go with you today. I need to do something for my aunt–it’s urgent.
Can we go next week instead?
Well, that’s all right.
How about I’ll tell Uncle Yod to take you there in the afternoon instead?
Mhm.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
So, are you usually always this busy?
Why do you ask?
Well, you’ve been staring at your phone since we arrived here.
Yes.
You’re busy?
You’re nosy!
Well, I’ve ordered Chicken Nanban for you.
I don’t know if you’ll like it.
Oh, here they are!
Thank you.
Wow, it looks so tasty. Thank you. That one is for you.
You ordered them, so eat them yourself. Hurry up so we can go home.
Do you have to do something after this? Why are you in a rush?
Yes, I have to go somewhere.
Where is it? Can I go with you?
Just mind your own business.
I only agree to take you here because my aunt said so.
Stop asking so many questions–it’s annoying.
And quit using that stupid voice. Why would you do that? It sounds so awkward.
If you think it’s cute, I’m telling you it’s giving me a creep.
Wait, where are you going?
Toilet.
So pretty, look. See this?
Aww, don’t tell me you already ordered it.
But of course, I did.
Oh.
Jee, what’s wrong, dear?
Fai just ditched me, Mum.
She completely ignored me.
She took me out to eat but…
she barely said a word to me. She just ate and left.
Where did she go then?
I don’t know! She said something urgent  came up, then she just left me there alone.
Something urgent?
Why are you dropping me off here, Uncle Yod?
Well, Young Master told me to drop you off here. She’s probably waiting inside.
I see.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
I thought you said you were busy.
You’re here?
It’s for you. These too.
Eat, so we can get going.
I finished earlier than expected.
My aunt made me go on a date this morning.
Really? How was it?
Nothing much. It was pretty annoying.
Don’t you feel anything when I go out with someone else?
What should I feel then?
Don’t you want to ask me anything?
What should I ask then?
You, nitwit.
Time to go now.
Huh? Is she mad again?
- Here.
- Thanks.
Do you come here often?
No.
You seem to know your way around here though.
Have you ever heard of an internet? Try using it.
This is good.
Try it.
Have a bite.
Wouldn’t you be in trouble if Miss Panee knows you’re here with me?
She doesn’t know. I told Uncle Yod to pick you up, remember?
What about when we go back?
You can walk home then.
You seem different lately.
How?
You’ve never been this nice to me.
All you did was keep picking a fight.
That’s because I…
I…
I want to go on that slide.
Let’s go then.
What?
Come on. Get moving.
I haven’t put on a life jacket yet.
Go put it on over there.
Do we have to do it now?
Or we won’t get to do it.
- It’ll be too crowded.
- No one’s going to play it.
There’s so many people over there.
♫Where’s that love people are saying?♫
♫To always be by each other’s sides♫
♫The love that’s willing to sacrifice everything♫
♫Everything even my own life♫
♫Do they really exist? I’d rather not believe it♫
♫I don’t think I’ll ever fall for anyone♫
♫Love? I don’t find it interesting♫
♫Sorry about that♫
♫But then who are you?♫
♫To make my heart keep fluttering♫
♫Please tell me♫
♫What’s happening with my heart?♫
♫It can’t be, why am I feeling this?♫
♫Oh, my heart is pounding so fast♫
♫Time freezes whenever I see you♫
♫I wonder why every time you smile♫
♫Something in your eyes make me go weak♫
♫Oh no, this is real–it’s not a dream♫
♫Or is the love that people are saying...♫
♫Is it you?♫
The weather is so nice.
You seem to like it here a lot.
I do. I miss those times when I came here with my dad.
I’m sure your dad already knows you come back here today.
This place has changed so much.
I wonder what he’s like now.
He’s probably having a good time up there.
Your dad might have run into my mum by now.
They’ve probably become friends.
I’ll ask Dad to tell your mum that you like to pick on me.
Surely, Mum will know I got falsely accused by a silly Gremlin.
Don’t you remember anything about your mum?
I only saw her in the picture.
But I could feel that she loved me so much.
You might be stubborn, hot-headed, and a bit of a bully.
But I’m sure your mum loved you a lot.
Just like Uncle Ak, he also loves you a lot.
Don’t rub it on my face.
You stole my dad’s love from me.
I’m serious. Uncle loves you so much.
I don’t know what’s going on between you and your father.
But I can feel that you both really love each other.
I want you to put your bias aside, and open up to him while you still can.
Don’t be like me and wait until he’s gone.
As someone who no longer has a dad and a mum, that’s all I could say.
Hey.
What?
Can you take a picture for me?
Right here, it’s so pretty.
Sure.
Make sure I look tall.
1 2 3. Again, 1 2 3.
I’m so good at this.
It’s because the model is pretty.
Okay, not so bad.
Here, do it for me too.
Take it. You’re not the only one who wants a picture here.
Make it look nice.
Sure.
1 2 3. Here, take a look.
Let me see.
Hmm, you’re better than I thought.
Let’s take a picture together.
Why?
As a reminder…that we once came here together.
Come on.
Ready?
- Wow.
- Is it good?
So pretty.
Wow, look at the view there.
But I look prettier. Look.
Thank you for taking me out today.
If you’re feeling grateful, you should do it properly.
You need to list out all the things I’ve done for you. So that you won’t forget them.
Did you do it because you expected something in return?
Or just to hold it over my head later?
You always think badly of me.
I just want you to see…
that I can be nice too.
I don’t think badly of you.
Then, smile a bit.
What for?
Please. To end the day happily.
Smile like this.
Happy now?
I’m going in.
Are you here to see Kaphrao?
I’m here to see you. Can we talk?
I’m busy.
It’s about Kaphrao.
It won’t be long.
Go on then.
Kaphrao and I have known each other for so long–since when we were in school.
You know how I feel about her, don’t you?
So what?
I came back this time because I intend to never let her go again.
Why are you telling me this?
Go tell her then.
I saw you with her but I really can’t tell what relationship it is that you have with her.
Let me get this straight then.
If you don’t have feelings for Kaphrao, can you please step aside?
Don’t give her hope if you’re not serious about her.
You’ve split up with Jee since afternoon.
Why are you only home now?
I went out somewhere else.
With whom? What’s their name? Do I know them?
I’m a grown-up now, Auntie. You don’t need to be so worried.
I can take care of myself.
That’s right. Now, I’m just a bother to you, aren’t I?
You don’t listen to me anymore.
Come on, Auntie. Please don’t be upset. It was really for work.
I know that sometimes you find me annoying.
But it’s all out of good intentions.
I want you to be with someone you deserve, and only have the best things in life.
I know.
You know how much I love you, don’t you?
If you love me, don’t ever let me down, okay?
Yes.
I’ll take that as a promise.
[Nod]: I came back this time because I intend to never let Phrao go again.
Let me get this straight.
If you don’t have feelings for Kaphrao, can you please step aside?
Don’t give her hope if you’re not serious about her.
[Panee]: If you love me, don’t ever let me down, okay?
[Fai]: It’s really good.
Let’s take a picture together.
Come on.
Ready?
[Phrao]: Thank you for taking me out today.
♫I still remember vividly that day when we first met♫
♫Those memories we had together never fade away from my heart♫
Thank you, Phi Jah, for taking me out today.
♫We might never say it out loud how we feel for each other♫
♫But deep down we both know how we feel♫
♫Those things in the past, I still can’t forget them♫
♫I want to know if you’re like that too–do you also feel the same?♫
Phi Jah, please don’t leave me! Fai!
Fai!
♫I could never forget those eyes of yours♫
♫The warmth you used to give me, I still remember it vividly♫
Stop bullying her!
♫No matter for how long, you’ll always remain in my heart♫
Phi Jah.
♫All those years I’ve been waiting, for us to finally be together again♫
♫I could never forget those eyes of yours♫
♫The warmth you used to give me, I still remember it vividly♫
♫No matter for how long, you’ll always remain in my heart♫
♫All those years I’ve been waiting, for us to finally be together again♫
[Next Episode]
[Fai]: I need to go to Bangkok with Dad.
I won’t be able to take you out this weekend.
Let me help you, Miss.
Miss Kaphrao!
Miss Panee wants to see you right now.
My friend is here with her daughter.
I want you to take us to see the cave in the mine.
I don’t understand why we have to go see that stupid cave in the mine.
That damn girl is extremely afraid of the dark and narrow space.
Help…
Kaphrao!
♫I still remember vividly that day when we first met♫
♫Those memories we had together never fade away from my heart♫
♫We might never say it out loud how we feel for each other♫
♫But deep down we both know how we feel♫
♫Those things in the past, I still can’t forget them♫
♫I want to know if you’re like that too–do you also feel the same?♫
♫I could never forget those eyes of yours♫
♫The warmth you used to give me, I still remember it vividly♫
♫No matter for how long, you’ll always remain in my heart♫
♫All those years I’ve been waiting, for us to finally be together again♫
[North Star Entertainment]
[Flaming Chains of Love]